Alright ok ok ok ok
Alright ok
BABYMONSTER
I got no worries on my mind
I’m never gonna stop
난 멈추지 않아
So you can say goodbye
I’ll fulfill my fantasy
And you can watch and see
Why don’t you clap for me
박수나 쳐보지
Shine so bright
눈부셔
They say she looking flawless
I know
I was born like this
타고났지 Like this
She’s unlike unlike anybody
Here, there going crazy everywhere
여기저기 다 난리 난리
A.B.C.D.E.F.G. She’s baddie
가나다라마바 싸가지
Gotta gotta go so c’est la vie
I’m dancing in the moonlight
Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh
Ooh ooh ooh ooh ay
Can’t stop this feeling tonight
What you waiting for
Baby it was all a dream
You thought I was yours
Don’t get it twisted
멋대로 착각하지는 마
It’s bitter it’s sweet
High up in the sky
저 하늘 높이
I’m spreading my wings
Like I’mma live
Forever
Like I’mma live forever
Like I’mma like I’mma
Forever
Like I’m gonna live
Like I’m gonna live forever
OK you know what it is
I'm that nice
I’m that nice 뭘 것 같아 너와 내 차이
What’s the difference between me and you
Pull up on me pay the price
Put a milli on a rock my type
Never seen it in your life
Pretty
예뻐 그러니까 바빠
That’s why I’m busy
Yeah I’m bad
아니 나빠 온 세상 울리는
Making the world cry bad girl
Bad girl
B (B) A (A) B (B) Y (Y) M (M) O (O) N
Get money
Bout it bout it
Bout it bout it 발끝까지 까지
Head to toe
Ride the rhythm
리듬 타지 타지 기분 짜릿짜릿
Thrilling feeling
Everybody get down
Roll up on ‘em with the motor running
I’mma give you something
Bet you put the money in the bag
I’m dancing in the moonlight
Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh
Ooh ooh ooh ooh ay
Can’t stop this feeling tonight
What you waiting for
Baby it was all a dream
You thought I was yours
Don’t get it twisted
멋대로 착각하지는 마
It’s bitter it’s sweet
저 하늘 높이
High up in the sky
I’m spreading my wings
Like I’mma live
Forever
Like I’mma live forever
Like I’mma like I’mma
Forever
Like I’m gonna live
Like I’m gonna live forever
I can see the bright horizon
Overcoming the world
세상이란 벽을 넘어서
No nothing can stop me now
We forever forever
Forever ever ever
Ooh ooh
Baby it was all a dream
You thought I was yours
Don’t get it twisted
멋대로 착각하지는 마
It’s bitter it’s sweet
High up in the sky
저 하늘 높이
I’m spreading my wings
Like I’mma live
Forever
(Forever ever ever)
Forever (We forever forever forever ever ever)
Forever
Like I’m gonna live
Like I’m gonna live forever